gty.org 2015-06-10

# Grace to You

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” (IP) address. When a visitor requests a page from our website, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site.

We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record email addresses of the visitors.

**What are cookies?**

From time to time, Grace to You may send a cookie to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk, it can’t read cookie files created by other sites, and it can’t damage your system

Grace to You may use cookie and tracking technology, depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**What other information do you request?**

We may also request your email address or mailing address for the purposes of providing additional services or information or materials you have requested.

Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy, which means we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your email address to a third-party, without your consent.

In addition, Grace to You will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. We do however send an email acknowledgment when you send an email to Grace to You, or send a comment through our guestbook.

If you choose to purchase something online, we need to know your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and card expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

Grace to You uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. However, Grace to You will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on gty.org; 
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Grace to You, or visitors to gty.org; 
  * Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties; 
  * Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. 

**What responsibility do you take for third party links?**

In an attempt to provide increased value to our users, we may provide links to other websites or resources. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and do not endorse and are not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for the privacy practices or the content (including misrepresentative or defamatory content) of such websites, including (without limitation) any advertising, products or other materials or services on or available from such websites or resources, nor for any damage, loss, or offence caused or alleged to be caused by, or in connection with, the use of or reliance on any such content, goods, or services available on such external sites or resources.

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

The Grace to You website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites. We do not share any of the individual personal information you provide with any other site, linked or otherwise. However, we may share non-personal, aggregate data (i.e., how many visitors, page views, etc.) with other sites.

You may check with the sites to which we link to determine their individual privacy policies. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online—for example through email, discussion lists, or elsewhere—that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

**Your Consent to This Agreement**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Grace to You as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
